[male announcer]
And now. Hattie’s Tea Party.
with your hostess with the mostest:
Hattie Tetch!
Good evening. Gotham.
Crime. It's a plague in our city.
and no one seems to be looking for a cure.
[dramatic music playing]
[Hattie] Nightly gunfire and bloodshed
have become routine in Gotham.
None of us are safe.
Commissioner James Gordon
and his officers
have turned our streets
into a war zone.
[explosion]
And matters are only made worse by
the interference of a masked outlaw
whose true agenda remains unknown
to the good citizens of Gotham.
- [grunting]
- [laughing]
[grunts]
[Hattie] And while we cower in our homes.
the G.C.P.D. spends its time harassing one
of Gotham’s most esteemed businessmen.
If you’ve been following my coverage
of Rupert Thorne’s trial.
then you know that the case
against him is gossamer thin.
Rumor has it. D.A. Peter Mitchell
has found a surprise witness
to bolster his flimsy prosecution.
But they don’t call me the Mad Hatter
of News for nothing.
I did get the name for you.
dear ones.
Now. we can all hear
what surprising comments
Thorne’s accountant. Julian Gregory. makes
when he’s flown to testify this week.
Some of Mr. Gregory’s colleagues
refer to him as “Calendar Man”
because of his eidetic memory
when it comes to dates and times.
That should make it very easy for him
to remember the day that he was--
[panting]
[male guard] Is there a problem.
Mr. Thorne?
[exhales] Yeah. I need a new television.
And Julian Gregory has to die.
[theme music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[dramatic music sting]
[Alfred] Are we certain that Gotham
International is out of the question?
The D.A.’s office won’t put Gregory
on a commercial flight.
Gordon will use one of
the smaller airports.
I would think that
the Commissioner would simply
tell you the whereabouts
of this accountant.
I work alongside the police. Pennyworth.
That doesn't make me one of them.
But with the professional relationship
you have with Barbara Gordon.
her father should
extend more trust.
Our goals might be the same.
but our methods never will be.
Moldoff Airfield would definitely
suit the Commissioner’s needs.
So would the Burnly County airstrip.
Shall I investigate one
while you the other?
No. I'm taking your advice.
Oh? The father or the daughter?
[Batman] Barbara.
Sir. if you truly haven’t earned
the Commissioner’s trust.
he might not appreciate your attendance.
I might be uninvited.
but that doesn't mean I'm unexpected.
[car engine starts]
[prison door alarm buzzes]
[prison guard]
Your guest is here. Mr. Thorne.
Take a seat.
I'm hearing a lot of things
I don't like. Eddie.
Things about how my business
is being handled.
Mishandled by you.
It's that damn Batman!
- Every time we make a move. he--
- That lunatic is not top of the list.
Who is at the top. Eddie?
The accountant.
Good. Eddie.
It would also be good if tomorrow
he wasn't troubled with breathing anymore.
Oh. I'll find him.
If I gotta turn over every rock in Gotham.
- He's already been found.
- You got a mole in the G.C.P.D.
Diversify your portfolio. Eddie.
You diversify. you have options.
Options. Yeah... I'll remember that.
[dramatic music sting]
[Bullock]
You know damn well this isn't fair.
You put the bullet in Dent.
and I'm the one who loses his shield.
Relax. You'll get your shield back. buddy.
I'm working on it.
You been handing me that line for weeks.
and I’m fed up with it.
I'm not the only one with skeletons.
Flass. If I don’t get...
- Whoa. Where do you think you're going?
- Step aside. sister.
This meeting is for detectives only. officer.
No uniforms.
- Flass?
- Sorry. Sloppy Joe. Chain of command.
Hattie Tetch is annoying. but she’s right.
The D.A.’s case is shaky.
Julian Gregory is our last. best chance
to put Thorne away for good.
We need to protect Gregory and clamp a lid
on every detail about this case.
Thorne's broken every law in the book.
how does this case come down
to one witness?
Thorne's pockets are
as deep as his crimes.
That makes putting him away harder.
but we need to get it done.
It's our job to protect this city.
No one else's.
- [muttering] Yeah. you and your bat buddy.
- Something to say. Flass?
Absolutely not. sir. On the job. sir.
Protect this city.
[jazz music playing]
You're worthless!
Every one of you. Worthless.
What about me. Eddie?
Am I worthless?
- [groans]
- Not now. baby. I'm workin'.
Argh! You ruined my train of thought.
You were tellin' 'em all
how worthless they are.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. that's right.
Worthless!
Every single one of ya.
The Thorne Mob?
More like the Keystone Idiots!
Tonight. that's over.
Tonight. you're gonna
show me you got what it takes!
Show me you're bona fide!
- What's "bona fide"?
- Like this ring here.
- Eddie got it for me. It's the real deal.
- Shut up!
We run this town. see?
We run it.
and we’re gonna keep running it.
no matter what that sniveling accountant
squealing in court like a...
A pig! A mouse?
[screaming in rage]
[dramatic music playing]
The squealer goes tonight. Get me?
No mistakes. No excuses.
In the dirt.
[telephone ringing]
- This is Gordon.
- [Batman] Barbara.
Oh. hi. Let me guess.
you need some legal help?
[Batman] I need information.
Moldoff Airfield
or Burnly County airstrip.
where is your father
meeting the accountant?
Right. Of course.
Unfortunately. my father doesn’t
tell me case details.
He’s in danger. Barbara.
Withholding this isn’t helping him.
Okay. Fine. I guess. in the past.
he’s used Moldoff. but--
[hangs up]
- You made a good speech.
- Thanks.
And didn’t mention the Batman.
The Batman is an asset.
I appreciate what he does. but I won’t
rely on him to do this department’s job.
I’m not built that way.
- Neither am I.
- I know. I count on that.
[airplane approaching]
[Julian] Oh! Oh! Here’s another one.
What do James Polk and Warren G. Harding
have in common?
- I don't know. both were presidents?
- Same birthday! November 2nd. Scorpios!
[chuckles] What are the odds?
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music playing]
[maniacally laughing]
- [bullets ricocheting]
- Whoa. whoa!
[pained groan]
[screaming]
[airplane engine accelerating]
[yelps. grunts]
[Eddie] Whoo!
[maniacally laughing]
Die. squealer! Die!
- [whirling]
- [glass shatters]
[guns cocking]
[fighting grunts and groans]
[airplane engine whirring]
[screaming]
Come on. Eddie. Let's get outta here.
[suspenseful music playing]
[screaming]
Let go. ya freak!
I got nothing to... [screaming in pain]
[maniacal laughing]
[exhales]
Eddie. you didn’t have to do that.
Jimmy woulda never squealed.
That’s how a secret
stays secret. Dez.
Yeah. sure.
but when Mr. Thorne finds out...
But Thorne ain’t gonna find out
because that accountant’s gonna be in
the dirt before anybody tells him. Yeah?
Okay. Okay. All I'm saying is.
how you gonna do it. Eddie?
Don't worry about it.
I know a guy.
Dad told me you saved the accountant.
Now I need to know
where your father is keeping him.
Or you can just call him.
ask him yourself.
He can’t give me that information
without compromising himself.
But I can? Of course. I can.
I’m Barbara Gordon. public defender.
I’m always compromised.
Protecting Julian Gregory
is all that matters right now.
I don't know where he is.
- You can find out.
- Maybe.
If I cross a bunch of lines
that I'm never going to cross.
I won't spy on my father.
- You can trust me.
- I do.
I trust you'll find him on your own.
Without using me.
[sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
You know why you're here.
I need to get to the truth.
Sir?
Thorne knew when
and where Gregory was landing.
If we have a leak in this department.
I need you to plug it.
Sir. if there's a leak in the department.
we both know that it's F--
I thought you wanted to see me.
Commissioner.
But if you’re giving Montoya one
of your little pep talks. I can always...
Detective Montoya
is your new partner. Flass.
Sir?!
Great. She’s more of a looker
than the last one.
Another thing. Montoya’s the lead.
I want the two of you on Gregory.
Get him to the Chandler Arms
and sit on him until he testifies.
Montoya.
Watch your back.
[Eddie] What you got for us. Strange?
Professor. please.
I worked long and hard for that title.
- Mister... Nygma. was it?
- Eddie's fine.
The things I make are expensive.
But the knowledge to make
them untraceable?
- There’s no upper price on that.
- Understood.
When we get rid of the Batman.
Gotham will be ours.
This way.
And this is?
Power. Strength. Aggression.
All beyond the limits of any man.
Or rodent. flying or otherwise.
- Price?
- Consider it a field test.
The Batman is an interesting
environmental hurdle.
I would like to see how my formula
does in a... human trial.
Y’know. what. prof?
I definitely wanna see that too.
[shower running]
[Thorne] Towel.
Towel. goddammit!
[suspenseful music sting]
If you’re here to apologize for
slicing my ear. don’t worry about it.
It healed up good as new.
It’s like you never even touched me.
Nothing to say. Strong and silent. huh?
Is this supposed
to turn my spine to jelly?
You’ve got it backwards. freak.
If you’re here.
you’re the one who’s running scared.
I’m gonna beat this rap.
And when I do. I am going to make it my
mission in life to burn... [groans]
[straining] Go on! Do it!
[straining]
I knew it. You don’t have the stones
for the real dirty work.
That’s why I’m gonna win.
[grunting]
Gordon thinks that safe house
of his is Fort Knox.
He’s dreaming.
I can put my finger on Gregory anytime.
anywhere. Bank on it.
The accountant has seen his last sunrise.
[groaning. grunting]
You’re going to burn. freak.
Bank on that too. You will burn!
[dramatic music playing]
Pennyworth. which G.C.P.D. safe houses
are still active?
[Alfred] The Adams Garage.
the Chandler Arms.
and the Ward Street Church.
Three stops. Done.
[engine revving. tires screech]
[Eddie] Look at that squealer.
Just like Rapunzel hiding in her tower.
[Dez] So what's the plan?
Do we shoot our way in?
No. Dez.
This job calls for something much bigger.
[chuckles]
And a helluva lot messier.
- Okay. What are we gonna use?
- Not what. Dez.
- Whom.
- [groans]
- [chuckling]
- [straining]
[maniacally laughing]
- [monstrous growling]
- [maniacally laughing]
Beautiful! You’re beautiful!
Now. what do we need to do?
[deep monstrous voice]
Kill the squealer.
Calm? Calm? How can I stay calm?
Thorne can find me here!
He can find me anywhere!
Relax. Detective Montoya here
is on the case.
We've kept this location a secret. Julian.
You'll be fine.
- [banging. rumbling]
- What the hell?
[suspenseful music playing]
Time to die. squealer.
Take it down!
[guns cock. shoot]
[fighting grunts and groans]
[yelps]
This is Montoya. I need backup
at Chandler Arms! Now!
[grunting]
You.
What the hell are you doing?
[grunts]
[shudders. groans]
[fighting grunts and groans]
Move your ass. Calendar Man!
[groaning]
- [grunting]
- [yelps]
Kill the squealer. [growls]
Move it!
[strained grunt]
- [cracking]
- [screams]
[high pitched ringing]
[distorted grunts]
[civilians chattering]
[suspenseful music playing]
[monstrous roar]
[fighting grunts and groans]
[snarling]
- [engine running]
- [tires screeching]
[grunting]
[engine revving]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting continues]
- [strained grunting]
- [tires squealing]
[straining]
[strained grunting. gasp]
[groans]
[dramatic music continues]
[wheezing]
[police sirens blaring]
On February 3rd.
I did inform Mr. Thorne
that the filings were inaccurate
and. uh... Unlawful.
And his response?
Mr. Thorne said.
“The law is whatever I decide it is.”
[crowd gasps and chatters]
Your witness.
Your honor. the defense moves
for a complete dismissal of all charges.
The prosecution’s case is nothing more
than a collection of tainted evidence
brought to us by a police department
famous for its corruption and ineptitude.
[dramatic music playing]
[clears throat]
The court has reached a verdict.
I’m prepared to rule this case a...
[Hattie. over radio]
As this reporter predicted.
the case against Rupert Thorne
was completely dismissed.
Despite the best efforts
of D.A. Peter Mitchell.
Commissioner Gordon and our circus
of a police department.
the day was overwhelmingly
Rupert Thorne’s.
- You okay. Dad?
- No.
- I'm far from okay.
- Thorne got to the judge.
We should've seen it coming.
Yeah. but you didn't.
because you're chumps.
You keep thinking Gotham's
gonna do right someday.
You need to get as far away from me
as possible. Flass.
[chuckles] Wake up. Nemo.
This ain't dreamland.
The energy here is electric.
Thorne’s exoneration symbolizes
the start of Gotham’s next chapter.
- Perhaps now some civility...
- [female reporter] Here they come!
[gasps] Oh! Here he is!
- [reporter 1] Here they are!
- [reporter 2] Mr. Thorne!
[overlapping chatter]
[reporter] Mr. Thorne. how does
it feel to be exonerated?
I hate this.
Thorne won this round. but if he thinks
this fight is over. he’s dead wrong.
Mr. Thorne. do you have a few words
you can share on this glorious day?
Nice hat.
[overlapping chatter]
Rupert Thorne. the brightest light
in Gotham is free to shine once more.
[dramatic music playing]
- Ouch.
- [British accent] I'm terribly sorry. sir.
Incompetent.
- I knew we'd beat 'em. Dad.
- We didn’t beat them. son. We own them.
Always keep a diversified portfolio.
my boy! Diversify. and you can’t lose!
[chuckles] Every goddamn
one of those suckers belongs to me.
[maniacal laughing]
- Dad? What's so funny?
- [laughing continues]
Dad. cut it out! You're scaring me.
Dad. stop! Stop laughing! Please!
[suspenseful music playing]
- [door creaks open]
- [Gordon] Barbara?
- Honey. why did you...
- Okay.
You two need to talk.
And you need to do it without me.
[door creaks shut]
Some in Gotham called
a so-called Batman
a hero.
But I ask you.
who appointed this anonymous vigilante
judge. jury and executioner
of Gotham City?
[dramatic music playing]
Murder. Robbery.
More in the last three weeks
than in all of last year.
You know. we just might crack this
working together.
Right. You always work alone.
I see our Mr. Riddler is escalating.
Now. it's a party!
One of Thorne's lieutenants
making his own moves.
I'm running things.
[laughing]
I really miss Harleen.
If they'd found her body.
at least we could grieve.
It's like she's still out there.
So. the last time we talked...
You tried to kill me.
Fair. I did.
But not very hard.
[gunshots]
Be careful out there. Barb.
Storm's getting rough.
Well. well...
what do we have here?
The whole city's on the verge of panic.
[intense music playing]
Everything this lunatic has done.
has been to destroy Gotham.
We need you to stop him.
I want him dead. do you get me?
Dead! Dead!
Dead. dead. dead. dead!
Strike him down. my children.
[grunts]
[grunting]
We are losing this fight.
Not a fight anymore. boss.
This new guy's making it war.
Good evening. Gotham.
It falls at dawn.
[chuckling]
All of you...
[laughing maniacally]
...will die.
[tense music playing]
[theme music playing]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today